sc-s.com 2017-11-18

# Privacy Policy – Swag Codes Spoiler

Effective  **02/2013** **Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:**

* Our Commitment To Privacy
* The Information We Collect
* How We Use Information
* Our Commitment To Data Security
* Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy
* How To Access Or Correct Your Information
* How To Contact Us

### **Our Commitment To Privacy**

****Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

###  **The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Swagcode Spoiler website. On some pages, you can make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

  * Email address
  * Phone number

### **The Way We Use Information:**

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

When you visit our website, we may assign your computer one or more cookies, to facilitate access to our site and to personalize your online experience. Through the use of a cookie, we also may automatically collect information about your online activity on our site, such as the pages you visit, the time and date of your visits, the links you click, and the searches you conduct on our site. 

We may allow third-parties, including our authorized service providers, IAC companies, advertising companies and ad networks, to display advertisements on our site. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. Our website does not provide any personal information to these third parties. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness. Some of these third-party advertising companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies ([www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)).

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

### **Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

### **Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy:**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

### **How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by visting the appropriate profile/signup pages. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

### **How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us e-mail to admin@sc-s.com
